# data from Opentdb.com

question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "DragonForce's Through the Fire and Flames; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language;Simlish; was The Sims (2000).",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in &quot;Clash Royale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Donkey Kong was originally set to be a Popeye arcade game.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in &quot;Sonic Generations&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Deus Ex (2000) does not feature the World Trade Center because it was destroyed by terrorist attacks according to the game&#039;s plot.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Half-Life 2, if you play the zombies&#039; speech in reverse, they actually speak coherent English.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Half-Life&quot; series, &quot;H.E.V&quot; stands for &quot;Hazardous Evasiveness Vest&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Minecraft wasn&rsquo;t the original name to Minecraft.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tony Hawk&#039;s extreme sports videogames revolve around performing professional BMX tricks.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
